关于这一点  我们将通过使sunshine应用
On that note, we're going to make our sunshine app
由网络连接到OpenWeatherMap的服务来极大地
100 times better now by connecting it over the network
提升其质量  OpenWeatherMap服务提供免费的天气的数据
to the OpenWeatherMap service. OpenWeatherMap provides a free weather data
和预报的API  网址链接就在下面
and forecast API. And the site is linked below, so
你可以点击了进去看看  通过浏览这个网站
you can follow along. By scrolling through the site,
你可以看到什么类型的数据是可用的
you can see what type of data is available. It
它还有示例查询  你可以点击这里
also has example queries so you can click on this
来查看在英国伦敦的天气情况
one to see what the weather is like in London.
返回的数据包括一个关于天气状况的对用户友好的说明
It includes a user friendly description of the weather
举个例子  比如这里的块云
condition, such as broken clouds, in this case. And
我们稍后会在应用中使用到这些数据
we'll use this later in our app. For the
如果想要获得完整的天气状况的列表  你可以返回
full list of weather conditions, you can go back to
到首页  向下滚动  然后点击
the main page. And scroll down. And then, click
这个链接来获取天气情况的编码
on this link here for the Weather Condition Codes.
在这个页面上  我们有了天气情况的
And on this page, we have the full list
完整列表  它涵盖了所有情况  从散云到
of weather conditions. It contains everything, from scattered clouds to
冻雨  甚至是火山灰  我不知道
freezing rain, or even volcanic ash. I don't know
你那里的情况  但愿希望它不会经常发生
about you, but hopefully that doesn't happen too often.